Lucas Su

https://lucassul.github.io/my-personal-website/

lijie.su93@gmail.com

0466-351-350

I'm a full-time Master's student in Computing and Innovation at the University of Adelaide, expecting to graduate in mid-2024. During my six years at Atkins (July 2016 - July 2022) as an Urban Planner, I contributed to over 20 projects, managing three as the project manager. This experience enhanced my design skills and demonstrated proficiency in project management.

Currently, I am committed to leveraging computer technology to empower businesses, aiming to facilitate a more enriched and smarter lifestyle. As a developer and former designer, I aim to bring a unique blend of skills driven by curiosity, rapid learning, and a steadfast commitment to making a positive impact on humanity. Outside of work, I enjoy skiing, riding, surfing, and spending time with my cat.

SKILLS

Front-End Development

- · Proficient in utilizing framework like React and Bootstrap to develop high-quality, responsive webpages.
- · Experience with Typescript to ensure robust development.

Back-End Development

- · Skilled in Node.js, Express.js, PostgreSQL (including Supabase) and MySQL.
- · Capable of building RESTful APIs and conducting testing using Postman.

Agile Development: Familiar with and recognise Agile development and Scrum methodologies.

Version Control: Experienced in using Git and GitHub for collaboration and version control.

Engineering Drawing: Proficient in creating engineering-style diagrams using AutoCAD and relevant plugins.

Graphic Design: Proficient in Photoshop, Illustrator for content layout and the creation of high-quality analysis diagrams.

Modelling & Rendering: Using SketchUp to create detailed 3D digital models and rendering with V-Ray/Lumion.

Report Writing: Skillful in Markdown and PowerPoint for effective and high quality presentation design.

PROJECTS

Personal Website - live: https://lucassul.github.io/my-personal-website/

- · Developed a fully responsive website using React and Bootstrap, featuring dynamic navbar behaviour.
- · Implemented varies animation hooks for components upon their initial appearance to enhance user engagement.
- · Utilized state-controlled form submission functionality to collect user input for data management and analysis.

Full-Stack Project - live: https://lucassul.github.io/todav-i-learned/

- · A published website where users can post and vote on facts.
- · All data is stored in Supabase and filtered at the database level.

EXPERIENCE

Atkins - Asia Pacific

July 2016 - July 2022

Urban Planner / Project Manager

- · Led land use planning and index balancing, customized to comply with local regulations and meet clients' requirements.
- · Conducted digital modelling and rendering for urban design, and drew anylysis diagrams to illustrate key design ideas.
- · Collaborated multidisciplinarily, to address complex issues and deliver optimal outcomes to clients.
- · Established and maintained daily communication with clients, ensuring alignment of design needs and project timelines.
- · Prepared and compiled presentation reports and materials.
- · Monitored project financials, making adjustments as necessary to ensure budget adherence.

Achievements: As the youngest Project Manager in the office, I successfully delivered multiple high-quality projects to clients, including Global 500 companies. Notably, one of these projects achieved the highest profit margin of the year, reaching an impressive 45%.

Atkins - Asia Pacific Nov 2015 - Feb 2016

Project Planner Intern

I contributed as a member of a 3-person planning team, responsible for modeling, rendering, and analyzing diagrams. Our project ultimately triumphed over competitors from Surbana Jurong Group and Boston Consulting Group (BCG).

EDUCATION

The University of Adelaide

July 2022 - July 2024

Master of Computing and Innovation: overall average score: 89/100 (GPA: 6.5/7.0), 30% Global Citizen Scholarship (highest standard).

Beijing University of Civil Engineering and Architecture

Sep 2011 - July 2016

B.Eng. in Urban Planning: 5-year average score: 86/100, TOTO Environmental Fund Winner, Cadre of Youth Volunteer Association, member of the committee in charge of studies